playtruckgames.net 2012-12-15

# Privacy Policy -

Privacy Policy for www.playtruckgames.net 

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us.

At www.playtruckgames.net, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.playtruckgames.net and how it is used. 

**Personal Information**  
Any personal information that you provide to our web site shall stay absolutely safe, private, and secure. We do not resell personal information to outside sources. 

**External Links**  
This site contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

**Security**  
We have taken the appropriate steps and followed industry standards to secure any personal data stored by our systems. 

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, www.playtruckgames.net makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
www.playtruckgames.net does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. 

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense . 

* Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet. * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. 

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.playtruckgames.net send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

www.playtruckgames.net has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.playtruckgames.net's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. 

Welcome to [play truck games](http://www.playtruckgames.net/) site. If you are already a truck games fun or you are new in this kind of games you are in right place. This site is combination of best truck games and monster truck games on net. [ play truck games](http://www.playtruckgames.net/) are popular site and you have a lot of games to play. You have great opportunity to drive excellent truck games in different environments, as the beach, mountain, or driving your 18 wheelers through the snow in Arctic route in [**_Ice Road Trucker 2_**](http://www.playtruckgames.net/game/130/Ice-Road-Trucker-2.html). Also you can be a rough player if you play some of our monster truck games as is [**_Monster Truck America_**](http://www.playtruckgames.net/game/1009/Monster-Truck-America.html). All games are with excellent graphics and realistic models of vehicles. In some games you can choose your terrain and customize your truck. They are all realistic and offers players all the time fun.   
You will have a lot of adventures while you drive [**_eighteen wheelers_**](http://www.playtruckgames.net/game/421/18-Wheeler-3.html) truck through the roads, delivering goods, but you must to keep the condition of the truck. To be a truck driver is funny and responsible job. Or you can drive around crushing lot of cars with your [**_monster truck_**](http://www.playtruckgames.net/category/4/Monster-Truck-Games/1.html).   
[**_Truck games_**](http://www.playtruckgames.net/category/1/Truck-Games/1.html) are always popular. Now we have really realistic games with work truck like large [**_dump trucks_**](http://www.playtruckgames.net/game/602/Dump-Truck.html), [**_mining trucks_**](http://www.playtruckgames.net/game/536/Mining-Truck.html), [**_tractors_**](http://www.playtruckgames.net/game/585/Tractors-Power.html), and the best is because all this trucks have a lot of raw power.   
Truck games is amazing as you can relax and have a great time. In fact these are not meant to be only for kids but even the adults can have their piece of fun and joy while playing such games. All truck games are free. If playing truck games is your type of sport you are in right pace.
